Guide to the Lee Family Papers, 1754-1836
Department of Special Collections
- ORIGINAL LETTERS AND DOCUMENTS
  - C (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 46. 1795, June 11. Newcastal. Wm. Coulson to Maj. Lee. Continent. A.L.S. disembarked, saddle, Goodwin and Gibson.
    - 47. 1785, Nov. 16.Maidstone. _____ Cousins to [Lee?] N.P. A.L.S. financial.
    - 48. N.D. May 1.Mews. Wm. Cowden to Cornet Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Cowden's mother talked to Lady Harcourt who will speak to Lord Harcourt.
    - 49. N.D. Aug. 31.Wm. Cowden to Lee. Maidstone. A.L.S. cream colored stallions
    - 50. N.D. Mar. 3.Mews. Wm. Cowden to Capt. Lee N.P. A.L.S. Lee to acquaint his father with the situation of his affairs, financial, Maj. Gardner, secret.
    - 51. N.D.Mews. Wm. Cowden to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S.
    - 52. 1800, Apr. 5.India House [London].M. Craig to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. to join his ship to sail from Gravesend, arrangements for Lee's passage.
    - 53. 1800, Apr. 8.Gravesend. M. Craig to Lt. Col. Lee. London. A.L.S. passage arrangements.
    - 54. 1800, Apr. 10.Gravesend. M. Craig to Wm. Lee. London. A.L.S. passage arrangements.
    - 55. [1794] Mar. 29.[Constr_n?] C. [Crauford] to Capt. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. 2 lost horses.
    - 56. 1795, Mar. 17.York House. C. [Crauford] to Gen. Harcourt on the Continent. A.L.S. Duke of York wishes detachment of 16th Lt. Dragoons to be completed and made ready for embarkation.
    - 57. 1791, Jan. 17.London. E. Crawford to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. bill.
    - 58. 1791, Feb. 24.London. E. Crawford to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. debt of Mme. Grandmaison.
    - 59. 1792, June [16].Kentish Town. Sarah Crode to Wm. Lee, Esq. Hartwell. A.L.S. found Lee's dog.
    - 60. 1795, Sept. 30.Camp near Delmenhorst. Thomas Crowder to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. remount, accounts, Sir R. Laurie.
    - 61. 1793, Oct. 5.London. George Crozier to Wm. Lee. Duke of York's Army on Foreign Service. A.L.S. clothing made and sent.
    - 62. 1797, May 18.London. George Crozier to Maj. Lee. Beaconsfield. A.L.S. lodgings.
  - CARMICHAEL, COOPER (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1. 1791, June 14.[Mauldslie] Andrew Carmichael to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. journey, finances, colts.
    - 2. 1791, Aug. 17.Mauldslie. Andrew Carmichael to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. finances, purchase of promotions, horse.
    - 3. 1792, Jan. 29.Mauldslie. Andrew Carmichael to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. sober life, greyhounds, Col. Gardner and Jamaica Regt.
    - 4. 1792, Mar. 5.Bourrowbridge. Andrew Carmichael to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. to rejoin army.
    - 5. 1793, Jan. 24.Barnet. Andrew Carmichael to Lt. Lee. London. A.L.S. bill, finances, regt. news.
    - 6. 1793, Feb. 9.Barnet. Andrew Carmichael to Lt. Lee. Sturbridge. A.L.S. recruiting, Sir Robert.
    - 7. 1794, Feb. 11.London. Andrew Carmichael to Capt. Lee. Audenarde, Flanders. A.L.S. promotions, Lee will be 2nd Major, Archer, Affleck, Boyce, Gen. Abercrombie, horses, Sir Edward Smith, the Duke called home, Lord Cornwallis arrived in London.
    - 8A 1794, Apr. 6.Mauldslie. Andrew Carmichael to Lee. N.P. A.L.S. promotions, horse, Lee to return to England, Gen. Dundas and Sir Robert.
    - 9. 1796, Apr. 13.N.P. Heary Cooper to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.L.S. bill for Lee's servant.
    - 10. 1796, Nov. [25 or 28][London] John Cooper to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.L.S. bill for spurs.
    - 11. 1796, Dec. 9.[London] John Cooper to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.L.S. repeats #10.
    - 12. 1797, Feb. 3[London] John Cooper to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.L.S. bill again.
    - 13. 1797, June 3[London] John Cooper to Maj. Lee. Beaconsfield. A.L.S. thanks for payment.
    - 14. 1797, Mar. [8]Henley. [Thomas] Cooper to Maj. Lee. Beaconsfield. L. written for Cooper. Bridge's indenture.
    - 15. 1797, Mar. 22.Henley. Thomas Cooper to Maj. Lee. Beaconsfield. A.L.S. Wells needs help to prove innocence.
    - 16. 1797, Mar. 25.Reading. Thomas Cooper to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. publican acquitted.
    - 17. 1796, Dec. 3.Newport. Henry Couper to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.L.S. Col. Hompesch, Lee wants to purchase Lt. Colonelcy.
  - COLLYERS 1788-1795(George Lambert, Nathaniel and N[athaniel Jr.] (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1. 1788, Jan. 22.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Wm. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. financial.
    - 2. 1788, May 28.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Cornet Lee. Bronsweig. [Brunswick] A.L.S.
    - 3. 1790, Mar. 16.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Cornet Lee. Chichester. A.L.S.
    - 4. 1790, Sept. 29.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Cornet Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. brother improved, financial.
    - 5. 1790, Nov. 9.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. no notification from War Office of Lee's captaincy.
    - 6. 1791, Feb. 17.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Lt. Lee. Hartwell. [A.L.S.] purchase lottery tickets.
    - 7. 1791, Feb. 19.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Lt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. congratulations on lieutenancy.
    - 8. 1791, Aug. 5.Lisle St. Mr. Collyer to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.N.
    - 9. 1791, Oct. 25.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S.
    - 10. 1792, Jan. 6.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S.
    - 11. 1792, Jan. 20.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.
    - 12. 1792, Apr. 25.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S.
    - 13. 1793, June 21.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Capt. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. business and financial, Maj. Boyce has been at point of death, lost horses.
    - 14. 1793, July 27.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Capt. Lee. N.P. A.L.S.
    - 15. 1793, Aug. 1 - Oct. 24, 1799.Collyer Account Book for Wm. Lee. A.D. of [N.] Collyer.
    - 16. 1793, Aug. 19.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Capt. Lee. N.P. [Continent?] A.L.S. sends things.
    - 17. 1793, Oct. 13.Lisle St. London. Nathaniel Collyer to Capt. Lee. with the Duke of York's army. A.L.S.
    - 18. [1794] Apr. 14.Lisle St. N[athaniel] Collyer to Cmdg. Officer, 16th Dragoons, Germany. A.L.S. wants arrears for 1793.
    - 19. 1794, May 14.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. French attacked Harcourt, Hawker badly wounded.
    - 20. 1794, June 17.Lisle St. Mr. Collyer to Capt. Lee. [Flanders?] A.L.
    - 21. 1794, Sept. 12.Lisle St. Messrs. Collyer to Cmdg. Officer, 16th Dragoons. N.P. A.N. Lee's promotion to Major and others.
    - 22. 1794, Sept. 12.Camp near Audenroon. Joseph Robinson A.D.S. note accepted by Capt. Lee. 1797, Mar. 2. Lisle St. Nathaniel and George Collyer to Maj. Lee. Reading. A.N.S. questioning above note.
    - 23. 1794, Sept. 17.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. congratulations on majority, two troops to embark.
    - 24. 1794, Nov. 12.Lisle St., London. Messrs. Collyer to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.N.
    - 25. 1794, Nov. 21.Lisle St., London. Messrs. Collyer to Cmdg. Officer, 16th Dragoons, Holland. A.L. want return of losses in service, to reimburse Lt. Gen. Harcourt.
    - 26. 1794, Dec. 6.War Office. Wm Windham to Messrs. Nathaniel and George Collyer copy. stoppage of 8 1/2 per day for each horse on passage to continent.
    - 27. 1795, Jan. 16.Lisle St. Messrs. Collyer to Officer comanding 16th Dragoons, Holland. A.L. return of arms wanted.
    - 28. 1795, Jan. 26.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Maj. Lee. Continent. A.N.S. is Joseph Fellows still living.
    - 29. 1795, Apr. 7.Lisle St., London. Messrs. Collyer to Officer comanding 16th Dragoons, [Lee?] N.P. Capt. Smith promoted to Major of 22nd.
    - 30. 1795, Apr. 9.Lisle St., London. Nathaniel and George L. Collyer to Maj. Lee. Continent. A.L.S. returns were not enclosed, equipment.
    - 31. 1795, May 12.Lisle St., London. Nathaniel and George L. Collyer to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. helmets and oilddecks.
    - 32. 1795, May 28.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Cornet Tudor. N.P. copy message for Lt. Col. Affleck.
    - 33. 1795, June 5.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Maj. Lee. Continent. A.N.S. Quarter Masters Murray and Tudor.
    - 34. 1795, June 11.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Maj. Lee. Continent. A.L.S. consignments, swords.
    - 35. 1795, Juee 23,Lisle St., London. Messrs. Collyer to Maj. Lee. Continent. A.N. Lt. Col. Henry Lord Paget from 80th Foot is notified to succeed Lt. Col. St. Leger in 16th Lt. Dragoons.
    - 36. 1795, June 25.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Maj. Lee. Continent. A.N.S. warrants.
    - 37. 1795, July 7.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to [Maj. Lee] N.P. A.L.S.
    - 38. 1795, July 21.Lisle St. Messrs. Collyer to Officer comanding 16th Lt. Dragoons, N.P. A.N. forwarding copy of letter of George Owen re: fraudulent claims against United Society for the Relief of Seamen and Soldiers, Widows, etc. 23 June 1795
    - 39. 1795, July 28.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Maj. Lee. Continent. A.N.S. swords.
    - 40. 1795, July 30.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Maj. Lee. Continent. A.N.S. swords.
    - 41. 1795, Aug. 14.Lisle St. Nathaniel and George Lambert Collyer to Officer comanding 16th Lt. Dragoons. N.P. A.N. amount of losses allowed has been paid.
    - 42. 1795, Sept. 11.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Maj. Lee. Continent. A.N.S. swords.
    - 43. 1795, Nov. 12.Lisle St., London. Messrs. Collyer to Maj. Lee. Germany. A.N.
    - 44. 1795, Dec. 1.Lisle St. Messrs. Collyer to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.N. Francis Campbell, Cornet in 16th.
  - COLLYERS 1796 - 1800 and N.D. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 1. 1796, Mar. 15.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Maj. Lee. St. Albans. A.N.S. regimental finances and business.
    - 2. 1796, Apr. 12.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.N.S. French groom.
    - 3. 1796, July 27.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Maj. Lee. Carnarvon, Wales. A.N.S. King to be at Weymouth, Harcourt wishes Lee to be present.
    - 4. [1796] Aug. 5.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Maj. Lee. Carnarvon. [A.N.S.?] can't help Lee with money.
    - 5. 1796, Sept. 30.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to Maj. Lee. Reading. A.N.S.
    - 6. 1796, Oct. 27.Lisle St. Messrs Collyer to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.N.
    - 7. 1796, Oct. 28.Lisle St. Messrs. Collyer to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.N. extract of letter from Maj. Smith and a note in another hand re: Gen. Dundas's Appendix.
    - 8. 1796, Dec. 13.Lisle St. Messrs. Collyer to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.N. forage money claimed.
    - 9. 1796, Dec. 20.Lisle St. Messrs. Collyer to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.N.
    - 10. 1797, Feb. 22.Lisle St. Nathaniel and George Collyer to Maj. Lee. Reading. A.N.S. surgeon Blyth.
    - 11. 1797, Mar. 6.Lisle St. Nathaniel and George Collyer to Maj. Lee. Hampstead A.N.S. Sgt. Smith's discharge.
    - 12. 1797, May 26.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Maj. Lee. Beaconsfield, A.N.S.
    - 13. 1797, June 22.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.N.S. congratulations on promotion.
    - 14. 1797, July 24.Lisle St. Nathaniel and George Collyer to Lt. Col. Lee. Maidenhead. A.N.S.
    - 15. 1797, Aug. 5.Lisle St. Nathaniel and George Collyer to Lt. Col. Lee. Guildford. A.N.S.
    - 16. 1797, Aug. 7.Lisle St. Messrs. Collyer to Lt. Col. Lee. Guildford. A.N.S. sends Lt. Col.'s commission.
    - 17. 1797, Sept. 29.Lisle St. Nathaniel and George Collyer to Lt. Col. Lee. Guildford. A.N.S.
    - 18. 1798, Jan. 22.Lisle St. Messrs. Collyer to Col. Lee. N.P. A.N.S. tamborine player fit to play in band.
    - 19. 1798, Feb. 1.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Col. Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. Richardson - cornetcy.
    - 20. 1798, Feb. 2.Lisle St. Nathaniel and George Collyer to Col. Lee. Guildford. A.N.S. Louis (?) going to India with 29th.
    - 21. 1798, Feb. 8.Lisle St. Nathaniel and Goerge Collyer to Col. Lee. Guildford. A.N.S. pay for regiment.
    - 22. 1798, Mar. 12.Lisle St. Nathaniel and George Collyer to Col. Lee. Guildford. A.N.S.
    - 23. 1798, Apr. 18.Lisle St. Nathaniel and George Collyer to Col. Lee. Guildford. A.N.S.
    - 24. 1798, July 12.Lisle St. Nathaniel and George Collyer to Col. Lee. Guildford. A.N.S.
    - 25. 1798, Aug. 5.Hounslow Barracks [N?] Collyer [Sr.?] to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. [A.N.S.] Quarter Master's accounts, Col. Affleck is wit the Admiral near Guildford.
    - 26. 1798, Sept. 21.Lisle St. Nathaniel and George Collyer to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.N.S.
    - 27. 1798, Nov. 27.Lisle St. Messrs. Collyer to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.N.
    - 28. 1799, Feb. 23.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.N.S.
    - 29. 1799, Feb. 26.Hounslow Barracks. Nathaniel Collyer to Col. Lee. Old Windsor. copy sending copy of letter of James Kibblewhite, Feb. 25, 1799re: attempts to arrest a debtor, District belonging to the Palace... is priveleged from arrests.
    - 30. 1799, Mar. 28.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Col. Lee. N.P. A.N.S. personal finances of Lee.
    - 31. 1799, Aug. [10]Lisle St. Messrs. Collyer to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.N. a question about Lee's account.
    - 32. 1799, Nov. 23.Hounslow Barracks. Nathaniel Collyer to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.N.S. re: ordering equipment and supplies, march.
    - 33. 1799, Dec. 4.Lisle St. George Lambert Collyer to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.N.S.
    - 34. 1800, May 9.Canterbury. Nathaniel Collyer to [Col. Lee] N.P. A.N.S. finances.
    - 35. N.D., Dec. 25.Hounslow Barracks. Nathaniel Collyer to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. re: recruiting bounties.
    - 36. N.D., Mar. 10.Lisle St. Nathaniel Collyer to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. regiment poorly clothed, reference to Gen. Harcourt, Mrs. Harcourt with Princess of Wales.
    - 37. N.D., Dec. 6.Lisle St. N[athaniel] Collyer to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. Lee's father has not yet paid for his equipment, George is mending.
    - 38. N.D., Mar. 31.Lisle St. N[athaniel] Collyer to Maj. Lee. Germany. A.N.S. promotions, Affleck to succeed Sir Robert Laurie.
    - 39. N.D., Oct. 2.Lisle St. N[athaniel] Collyer to Maj. Lee. Germany. A.L.S. Lee and Regiment to be coming home.
    - 40. N.D., Feb. 5.Lisle St. N[athaniel] Collyer to Lt. Col. Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. I hear that my son Natt is with you.
    - 41-45. N.D.N.P. 5 covers, 4 addressed to Lee and one to Officer Commanding 16th Lt. Dragoons upon the Continent and all docketed: Collyer.
  - D (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 1. 1788, July 7.Berlin. _____ Dacke to Lee. Brunswick. A.L.S. Capt. Mitchell, shipping china.
    - 2. 1796, Apr. 29.N.P. [James Dana] by Wm. Lee to Mrs. Harcourt. copy by Lee. re: Francis Dana in Lee's Regiment, father asks that son not be punished.
    - 3. 1792, _____ 18,.London. J. Davis to Wm. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. draft, financial, Prickett.
    - 4. 1792, _____ 21.London. J. Davis to Wm. Lee. [Thetford] A.L.S.
    - 5. 1792, _____ 22.London. J. Davis to Wm. Lee. [Thetford] A.L.S. Prickett, etc.
    - 6. 1785, Aug. 9.[Kensington?] Lane. [F?] Dax tp Cornet Lee. Maidstone. A.L.S. lost dog, can't sue.
    - 7. 1800, May 8.Windsor. Thomas Deane to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. tradesman wants payment.
    - 8. 1797, Apr. 30.Brunswick. _____ Delen to Wm. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. in French. Lee's studies at Strasbourg, Delon's trip to England, Mr. Fraser.
    - 9. 1787, June 26.[Bruton] St. _____ Delon to Wm. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. in French. gout, Comte de Cambis gone to join Regiment at Metz, Lee's mother sending vests, Lee Antonie.
    - 10. 1792, June 23.London. Henry Depois to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. in French. tailoring.
    - 11. 1792, June 30.London. Henry Depois to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. in French. shipment gone astray.
    - 12. 1792, July 12.[London] Henry Depois to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. in French. tailor.
    - 13. 1792, July 16.London. Henry Depois to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. in French. amount of bill.
    - 14. 1799, June 21.[London] Thomas C. [Devenish?] to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. bonds.
    - 15. 1798, [Mar.] 21.[London?] H. Dewar to Lt. Col. Lee. [London] A.L.S. received payment.
    - 16. 1799, May 16.Haymarket [London] H. Dewar to Lt. Col. Lee. Maddox St. [London] A.L.S. annuity.
    - 17. 1796, July 4.Conduit St. John Dewbery to Wm. Lee. Oxford. A.L.S. annuities.
    - 18. 1796, July 5.Conduit St. John Dewbery to Wm. Lee. Oxford. A.L.S. securities.
    - 19. 1799, June 13.Conduit St. John Dewbery to Col. Lee. Staines. A.L.S. Lt. Butter.
    - 20. 1799, Oct. 13.Conduit St. John Dewbery to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. Lt. Butter.
    - 21. 1796, Sept 14.Charing Cross. H. Dickson to Maj. Lee. Camp near Dorchester. A.L.S. business. [Calvert?]
    - 22 & 23. 1795, Sept 29.[_____horst?, Continent] George Don to Maj. Lee. Wulmstorf. A.L.S. cover with seal, Lt. Col. Carnegie, Gen. Clerfaye to occupy Frankfort, Austrians flying before the French.
    - 24. 1795, Dec. 1.Bremer Lehe. George Don to Lord Cathcart. N.P. A.L.S. transmits from Gen. Dundas the march route for 16th Dragoons and instructions, Lee to report to Nesbitt.
    - 25. 1795, Dec. 3.Bremer Lehe. George Don to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Dundas orders Lee also to take charge of a division of the 15th Dragoons on return to England.
    - 26. 1795, Dec. 7.Bremer Lehe. George Don to Col. Nesbitt. N.P. A.L.S. by direction of Dundas sends march route of 15th Dragoons, which after embarkation is to be under Lee's orders.
    - 27. 1795, Dec. 8.Bremer Lehe. George Don to Maj. Lee. N.P. L.S. Lee to put himself under command of Lt. Col. Carnegie of 11th Lt. Dragoons.
    - 28. N.D., Mar. 14.London. Peter Donnelly to Wm. Lee. King's Head, Coventry. A.L.S. a bill.
    - 29. N.D., Apr. 15.London. Peter Donnelly to Cornet Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. bill.
    - 30. N.D.,N.P. Peter Donnelly to Lt. Lee. King's Head, Coventry. A.L.S. Lee's account.
    - 31. 1790, Nov. 6.London. [Mme.] Dougé to Mr. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. in French. personal, invitation.
    - 32 & 33. [1790],[London] Mme. Doue to Mr. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. cover in French. Mme. Desincourt.
    - 34. 1797, Mar. 7.[Spetssenfields?] James Down to Maj. Lee. Hamstead. A.L.
    - 35. 1779, May 22.Harrow. James Drury to Master Wm. Lee. London. A.L.S. teacher sends instructions for study.
    - 36. 1786, Feb. 2.Aylesbury. B. Dudley to Cornet Lee. London. A.L.S. loans at interest.
    - 37. 1796, May 11.Marlbro. Thomas Duffin to Maj. Lee. N.P. [Newbury?] A.D. by order of Count Harcourt, Duffin to receive a sum of money.
    - 38. 1793, Oct. 18.Ostend. Gideon Duncan to Capt. Lee. Tournay. A.L.S. lost parcel.
    - 39. & 40. N.D.N.P. D. Dundas to Officer Commanding 16th Dragoons, Henley. A.L.S. and cover. possibility of disturbances being encouraged in the neighborhood of London in consequence of the present commercial difficulties.
    - 41. N.D., Oct. 1.St. James Hotel. _____. Dungannon to Capt. Lee. Flanders. A.L.S. bought majority, Harcourt went to Ireland - drinks, I hear.
    - 42. N.D., Oct. 11.South Marlbro. Dungannon to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. dinner invitation.
    - 43. 1796, May 13.N.P. James Dunn to Wm. Windham. Copy of letter by Wm. Lee, appeal for Dunn's son.
  - DERING, DESINCOUR (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 1. [1786], July 2.[Lurenden.] Cholmeley Dering to Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Canterbury Races in August, Lady Dering gone to Lambeth Palace.
    - 2. 1786, Nov. 13.[Lurenden.] Cholmeley Dering to Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Catterbury Races, with Lord Erroll to Margate, a ball, Sir R. Laurie, Hawker, army gossip.
    - 3. 1787, Jan. 15.Arras, Artois. Cholmeley Dering to Mons. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. hotels, complains about wines, Sir Edward.
    - 4. 1787, Feb. 5.Arras. Cholmeley Dering to Mons. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. Sir Edward's plans, Lee's father, white dog.
    - 5. 1787, Apr. 17.Arras. Cholmeley Dering to Mons. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. touring, to go to Paris, talk of war, dispairs of promotion, Sir James Pennyman.
    - 6. 1787, July 29.Dijon. Cholmeley Dering to W. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Capt. O'Hara.
    - 7. 1787, Sept. _____.Dijon. Cholmeley Dering to Mons. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. financial situation.
    - 8. 1795, Sept. 20.Canterbury. Cholmeley Dering to Maj. Lee. Continent. A.L.S. a Quarter Master, a review, wants a riding master, talk of dissolution of Parliament.
    - 9. 1788, Mar. 27.N.P. Zinette [Desincour] to [Lee] N.P. A.L.S. in French. almost illegible, personal - keep my secret - address in the name of Mme. Blanchet.
    - 10. 1788, Apr. 25.Paris. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 11. 1788, May 1.N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. Braunsweig. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 12. 1788, May 6.Paris. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. Brunswick. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 13. 1788, May 29.N.P. [Zinette] Desincour to M. Lee. Brunswick. A.L.S. in French. personal - votre amie pour la vie votre Josephine.
    - 14. 1788, July 5.N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. Brunswick. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 15. 1788, Sept. 4N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. Braunschweig. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 16. 1788, Sept. 11.N.P. [Zinette] Desincour to M. Lee. Braunschweig. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 17. 1788, Sept. 14.N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. Braunschweig. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 18. 1788, Sept. 19.N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. Braunschweig. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 19. 1788, Sept. 25.N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. Braunschweig. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 20. 1789, Mar. 2.N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. Chalons. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 21. 1789, Mar. 2.N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 22. 1790, Oct. 17.Marseille. [Zinette] Desincour to M. Lee. London A.L.S. in French. personal. la fin de notre afaire.
    - 23. N.D.,N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 24. N.D.,N.P. [Zinette] Desincour to M. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 25. N.D.,N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. Braunschweig. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 26. N.D.,N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 27. N.D., July.N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. Braunschweig. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 28. N.D., Sept. 29.N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. lee. Braunschweig. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 29. N.D.,N.P. Zinette Desincour to M. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. in French.
    - 30. N.D.,N.P. [Zinette] Desincour to Cornet Lee. Lewes. A.L.S. in French. personal, bitter.
    - 31. N.D.,N.P. [Zinette] Desincour to Cornet Lee. Lewes. A.L.S. in French. personal, sad.
    - 32. N.D., Feb. 18.N.P. Zinette [Desincour] to [Wm.] Lee. N.P. A.L.S. in French. personal.
    - 33. N.D.,N.P. Zinette [Desincour] to [Wm. Lee?] N.P. A.L.S. in French. personal, nearly illegible.
  - E (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1. 1783, Jan. 19.[Oxford] Edward Hyde East to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. asks Lee to visit.
    - 2. N.D., Feb. 22.N.P. Edward Hyde East to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. politics and professional studies, Calvert still at Cambridge.
    - 3. 1791, Nov. 26.Newmarket. James Edwards to Wm. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. bill of sale for horse (Duke of Bedford's)
    - 4. 1793, Mar. 25.London. Josiah Emery to Wm. Lee. Coventry. A.L.S. in French. asks payment.
    - 5. 1797, May 13.Reading. Thomas Eminson to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. exchange of commissions.
    - 6. 1794, July 10.London. Chris Emmott to Capt. Lee. Flanders. A.L.S. takes bond.
    - 7. 1796, Mar. 23.[London] Chris Emmott to Col. Lee. Henley. A.L.S. wants payment on bond.
    - 8. 1795, Nov. 30.Stade. [G.D. Ende] to unknown. translation. embarkation route for 16th Regt. Lt. Dragoons.
    - 9. 1788, June 7.Brunswick. Fred Erkel to M. Lee. Magdeburg. A.L.S. search for dog, Caesar.
    - 10. 1799, May 13.Kennington Cross. _____ Evans to Lr. Col. Lee. [London] A.L.S. re: an appointment.
    - 11. 1799, [Sept.] 16.Kennington Cross. _____ Evans to Lt. Col. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. annuity.
  - F (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1. 1790, Oct. 23.Rochester. Edmund Faunce to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. ordered to report for marine duty, Sir Robert, Col. Fox, Gen. Burgoyne, Lee's Company.
    - 2a. 1790, Nov. 12.27 Downing St. Edmund Faunce to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. drop the recruiting of independent companies immediately.
    - 2b. 1791, May 1.Strasbourg. [Fleuret] to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. in French. money matters.